# Yeganeh Salami



y.salami17@outlook.com



00989197285280



linkedin.com/in/yeganeh-salami-b30367b5



https://yeganesalami.github.io/

# Summary

Experienced Web Application Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in Python & C#. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Computer Software Engineering from Islamic Azad University Of Tehran North. https://yeganesalami.github.io/

# **Experience**



## **...** Web Developer

Asiatech Co.

Jun 2017 - Present (3 years 6 months +)

Participating as a developer in the backend of Asiatech mobile App and Asiatech Electronic customer care system. This project contains two parts, a Restfull API and an administrator control panel . Admin panel for designing mobile app or web app(e-care) dashboard, define different plans of internet services with differentcosts and other properties .The Restful API was aimed to give service to the mobile application and web application. Using Python, Django, Django REST framework, MariaDB, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Jquery, Bootstrap. Participating as a developer in customer club project. This project is for motivating customers to buy more and to conduct some actions to get points, using Python, Diango, Django REST framework, MariaDB, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Jquery, Bootstrap.

Participating as a developer in Asiatech Electronic customer care system. This project is to make customer able to pay their internet bills and to manage their internet services. Using Python, Django, Django REST framework, Redis, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Jquery, Bootstrap.

Participating as a developer in the Asiatech Portal project. Using C#, ASP.net, Sql server, stored procedure.

Participating as a developer in the Asiatech Portal Backend. Using ASP.NET MVC, ASP.NET Web API.

# Web Application Developer

saelTech

Jun 2016 - Jun 2017 (1 year 1 month)

Front-End Developer of Flight Reservation System. Using HTML, CSS, Javascript, React js, ASP.NET MVC. DeEextreme.

Front-End Developer of Customer Reservation management system. using HTML, CSS, Javascript, React js, ASP.NET MVC, DevExtreme



# **Software Supporter**

simorgh

May 2016 - Jun 2016 (2 months)



#### **Web Development Intern**

گروه مهندسین نیکان - Nikan Engineers Group

Mar 2015 - Jul 2015 (5 months) website designer

### **Education**

# Islamic Azad University North Tehran Branch

Bachelor's degree, Computer Software Engineering 2012 - 2016

### **Licenses & Certifications**



Bachelor - Islamic Azad University



Goethe-Zertifikat A1 - Goethe-Institut e.V.

Python (Basic) Certificate - HackerRank

4ddfb5f44a75

Problem Solving Certificate - HackerRank

665b85ec03a6

### **Skills**

Python • SQL • C# • ASP.NET MVC • Django • Git • Jira • Microsoft SQL Server • ASP.NET Web API • REST APIs